(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T22:43:15.279613",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
全世界、激震！
The whole world is shaken!
あの超大作が
That massive blockbuster...
ついに
...is finally...
スクリーンへ！！
...coming to the big screen!!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
The hope of humanity...
4人の「◯◯」に託された
...has been entrusted to four "censored".
なんだ？ここは！？
What is this place?!
どうして…こんなのひどいよ！
Why... this is too awful!
私のことはもういい！先に行け！
Don't worry about me! Go on ahead!
いろは～～～～！！！！
Iroha~~~~!!!!
あー！ふざけんじゃないよ！
Argh! You've got to be kidding me!
私たちの絆は
Our bond is...
永遠！
...forever!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
Together, we're going to save humanity!!
絶対に忘れないよ…
I'll never forget this...
自分史上、最高傑作です
It's my greatest masterpiece ever.
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は……この中にいる！
The killer... is among us!
えーーー！ / 俺ーーー！？
What---?! / Me---?!
きゃーーーー！
Eeeeeek----!
これは……
This is...
背後から刀で一振り……
A single strike with a katana from behind...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective-dono, what's wrong?
怪しい
Suspicious.
殺人犯と同じ場所にいられるか！
As if I can stay in the same room as a killer!
部屋に戻らせてもらう！
I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious.
……ふふふふふ
...Hehehehehe.
怪しい
Suspicious.
最初から最後までハラハラドキドキでしたー
It was thrilling and heart-pounding from start to finish!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！
My name is Hakui Koyori!
どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
An ordinary high school student you can find anywhere!
ただ一つ人と違うことは
The only thing different about me is...
科学が好き……ってところかな？
...that I love science, I guess?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ぅーー
Oh no! I'm gonna be late, late, late!
きゃーーー！
Eeeeeek---!
いったーい！
Ouch!
見つけた
Found you.
一緒にいるとなんか安心するでござる
Being with you makes me feel so at ease.
いただきますよー
Here I come!
くさい！ / 何すんだ！ / 無礼者！
Gross! / What are you doing?! / Insolent fool!
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The bittersweetness was exquisite!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた……！
Wh-What... You...!
holoX 4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！！
Did you actually search for "holoX 4th Anniversary"?!
決して、検索してはイケナイ
You must NEVER search...
「#SSholoX4周年」
..."#SSholoX4周年".
ルイ姉……
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから……
Iroha, it's okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
ばあ！
Boo!
（すごい悲鳴！）
(Screams!)
終始鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー
I had goosebumps the whole time!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa La lapata
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa Lapata palapa tapa
「迷宮なラビリンス」
"Labyrinthine Labyrinth"
No money 涸れた SHOW 招待状
No money, an exhausted show invitation
秘密で秘匿の異次元マンションへ！
To a secret, hidden cross-dimensional mansion!
ガタガタのドアの声に
At the voice of the rattling door,
No pain, no gain アンチェイン！
No pain, no gain, unchain!
狙う魔装のホークアイ
Hawkeye targeting demonic gear
迫る咆哮はウォークライ
The approaching roar is a warcry
放射状に突破口も どうだろう？の走馬灯
A radial breakthrough—how about that? A kaleidoscope of memories
Xに取り込まれてゆくよ…
Being absorbed into X...
刻印でござる～♪
It's a seal, de gozaru~♪
不条理な見学ツアー
An absurd sightseeing tour
ドアからドアへイリュージョン
An illusion from door to door
サーカス小屋よりピュアに響け笑い声！
Let laughter ring out purer than in a circus tent!
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa La lapata X！
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa La lapata X!
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa Lapata palapa tapa
つまり本件、
In short, regarding this matter,
力こそパワー的な
a "might makes right" kind of
「迷宮のラビリンス」
"Labyrinth of the Labyrinth"
並び立つシルエット
Silhouettes standing side by side
恐怖！秒で切断 Wi-Fi
Terror! Wi-Fi disconnected in seconds
これマジで最恐 Room だけど
This is seriously the scariest room, but
刃の回廊は普通に
The hallway of blades is normally
危ないって
dangerous!
One shot,
One kill
虚実踊るマリオネット
Marionette dancing between truth and lies
堕ちる部屋は何度目？っと
Which time is it falling into this room?
ランク外は眼中ないが
Unranked is out of sight, but
落雷あかんくない？
Isn't a lightning strike bad?
Xに取り込まれて ククク…
Absorbed into X, kukuku...
迷える子羊くんたちー！
You lost little lambs~!
お砂糖、スパイス、それとピンクなものいっぱい！ ハイになれるドリンクできたよー♪
Sugar, spice, and lots of pink things! A drink to get you high is ready~♪
ロックで飲んでくださいね ホロック スだけに
Drink it on the rocks, because it's holoX
ささ 皆様 飲むでござるー
Now, everyone, drink up, de gozaru~
吾輩 酔った
I'm drunk.
いや お前が飲むんかい
Wait, why are YOU drinking it?!
じゃあ とりあえず
Well then, for now,
かんぱーい！！
Cheers!!
鏡の回廊から 帝王の冷笑警報
From the corridor of mirrors, an emperor's sneering warning
塗り替えられる常夜に 爆ぜろ
In the repainted eternal night, explode!
笑い声！
Laughter!
お前たちもな！
You guys too!
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa La lapata
La lapata pa La lapata La lapata pa Lapata palapa tapa
さあ集え！ 5人の元
Come, gather around the five of us!
肩組んで 声を高らかに
Link arms and raise your voices high!
Lapata La La Lapata
エデンの海を超えるため
To cross the Eden Sea!
つまり本件、腹痛が痛い
In short, my stomach hurts so bad!
敵的な「迷宮の...
Like an enemy in the...
スーパーフューチャー パーティー ラビリンス」
Super Future Party Labyrinth"!
by holoX
イエーイ！
Yeah!
ということで！
And with that!
holoX 4周年！
holoX 4th Anniversary!
イエーイ！
Yay!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
めでたい！ ありがとう！
Congrats! Thank you!
よーし、張り切っていくぞー！
Alright, let's get fired up!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を...
So now, let's share our goals for our future activities...
早いね手が！ 早いね！
Your hand was so fast! So quick!
え、私から？ 聞いてないよ！
What, starting with me? I didn't hear about this!
どうしようかな... えーっと...
What should I say... Um...
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
えーっと、どうしようかな...
Um, what else should I say...
5年目も頑張るぞ！ holoX頑張るぞ！
We'll do our best in our 5th year! holoX will do our best!
頑張るぞー！
We'll do our best!
はい、じゃあ次、こちら！
Okay, next up over here!
はい！ えー、この5年目は...
Yes! Um, for our 5th year...
4人でもっと団結力をガッと強... ガッと...
The four of us will strengthen our teamwork even more, like BAM... BAM...
そろそろ日本征服ぐらいはしていきたいなと！
I think it's about time we conquer Japan!
確かにね！ 5年目だしね！ いいライン！
That's true! It's our 5th year! That's a reasonable goal!
日本征服頑張ります！
We'll do our best to conquer Japan!
怒涛で行くぞ！ はい、いろは氏！
Moving right along! Okay, Iroha-shi!
はい！
Yes!
皆さん、五... ござ... ござ...
Everyone, fi... Goza... Goza...
ということで5年目もね、元気に健やかに健康に活動頑張っていきたいと思います！
So for our 5th year, I want us to work hard while staying healthy, energetic, and happy!
holoX、5... 5年目頑張るぞー！
holoX will do our best in our 5... 5th year!
5周年まで頑張ろうね、また！
Let's do our best until our 5th anniversary too!
はい、じゃあ吾輩いいですか？
Alright, is it my turn then?
今年も...
This year as well...
生き残るぞー！
We will survive!
毎年言ってるよね！ でも生き残れたね、今年も！
You say that every year! But we did survive this year too!
そして！ 来年こそ...
And! Next year...
5年目こそ、我々の年にするぞー！
In our 5th year, we will make it our year!
するぞー！
We will!
ちょっとダサい... 待って、ダサい...
That was a bit uncool... Wait, so uncool...
なんでなんで？ みんな同じやつやっての！
Why, why? We were all doing the same thing!
こよリのダサさはどうでもよくて！
Never mind how uncool Koyori was!
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Everyone, take a look at this!
ライブステージ！
This live stage!
すごーい！ めっちゃカッコ良くない？！
Wow! Isn't it super cool?!
holoXの、最初のさ、登場からさ、うちかっこよかったよね！
Right from holoX's initial entrance, we looked so cool!
カッコよかった！
We really did!
助けられちゃったからね！
Because we got rescued!
このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて、色んな仕掛けがありますので！
This stage isn't just huge, it also has all kinds of features!
注目して、なんかね、出てきたりとか！
Pay attention, things might pop out or something!
出てきたり？！
Pop out?!
耳生え... 耳はもう生えてる！
Ears grow... Ears are already grown!
そして上がったりとか！
And rising up or something!
尻尾が顎に当たってる！
Your tail is hitting my chin!
変形したりとかさ！
Transforming or something!
合体とか！
Or combining!
さすがに無理だろ！ 合体！
Combining is definitely asking too much!
合体は無理だったんですけどー...
Combining wasn't possible, but...
そういうの大好きなんだけど、ちょっとさすがに holoX、予算が少なく...
I love stuff like that, but as expected, holoX's budget is a bit low...
当たり前でしょ！ こよリさんいくらかけてると思ってるの！
Of course it is! How much do you think was spent on this, Koyori-san?!
このステージ出来たからいいじゃん！
We got this stage made, so isn't that great!
ありがとう、こよりの凄さ認めてくれて！
Thank you for acknowledging how amazing Koyori is!
ということで、5年目もholoXerの皆さん、ぜひこんな...
So with that, all our holoXers, in our 5th year as well, please...
こんな我々ですけど...
We may be like this, but...
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
ちなみにここで、お知らせでございます！
By the way, we have an announcement right now!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると...
If you join the membership on the official Hololive channel...
なんと限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので、ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
You'll get to use exclusive emoji stamps, so please use them in the comments to hype things up!
さらに！ なんと今日からもう一つメンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども！
Furthermore! Apparently starting today, there's another membership perk!
先日発表した新曲「スキデカ」と「プライベートアイズ」の壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
You can also get wallpapers for our recently announced new songs "Sukideka" and "Private Eyes"!
マジで？！ 欲しい！ 俺たちが欲しい！
Seriously?! I want them! We want them ourselves!
はい！そして本日は何やらライブだけではなく
Yes! And today, it seems it's not just a live show...
通用な...
Normal...?
もりもりもりもり盛りだくさんらしいので！
Apparently it's super, super packed full of things!
もりもりもりもり盛りだくさん！
Super, super packed full!
皆さん最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
Make sure to watch properly until the very end!
途中退出禁止です！よろしくお願いします！
Leaving halfway is forbidden! Please enjoy!
もりもり... モリの字をつく...
Super packed... let's form the kanji for "mori"...
混ぜろよ！ 混ぜろよ！
Let me join! Let me join!
混ぜろよ！
Let me join!
ちょっと待ってください！
Wait a minute!
もう早くしないと！
We have to hurry!
みんなに見せられないから、ライブ！
Otherwise we can't show everyone the live show!
はい！早速！
Yes! Right away!
最初は...
First up...
ドゥクドゥクドゥク... 誰だ誰だ誰だ？
*Drumroll...* Who is it, who is it?
じゃん！ほい！こよちゃんのパートから！
Ta-da! Here! Starting with Koyo-chan's section!
イエーイ！
Yay!
なんだそのポーズ？絶妙にダサい...
What is that pose? It's awkwardly tacky...
可愛いか！
Wait, is it cute?!
帰るか！帰るか！
Should I head back? Should I go back?
あ、可愛い！こよちゃんいってらっしゃい！
Ah, cute! Have fun, Koyo-chan!
いってらっしゃい！ばいばーい！
Have fun! Bye-bye!
見てるよ！
We'll be watching!
走って！ほら急いで！広いから！
Run! Come on, hurry! The stage is big!
せかさないで！
Don't rush me!
じゃあ山田から行くよ。
Then Yamada will go first.
え、俺たちも？
Eh, us too?
早くして！早くして！
Hurry up! Hurry up!
早く行くぞ！
Let's go fast!
ラブ湧き発振 存在実態
Love surges and oscillates, actual existence
まじ感情 配合は未完成
Serious emotion, the formula is incomplete
ときめきのケミカル
Throbbing chemical
う～ん なるほど？ そんじゃこれならどう？
Hmm, I see? Well then, how about this?
加糖に新解法（ラボラトリー）
A new sugary solution in the laboratory
あわだつ心のポーション
Potion of bubbling hearts
混ぜるほどに甘くなるなる
The more I mix, the sweeter it gets
夢中／過剰なモーション
Obsessive, excessive motion
奇跡的においしくなれ！
Miraculously, turn tasty!
フラスコにハート ヤベーの出たと？
Heart in a flask, did something crazy come out?
ギミックのテスト？ 君が1番！
Gimmick test? You're number one!
ボーダレス 君になれ
Borderless, become yourself
ちょっと危険なまぜまぜ
A slightly dangerous mix-and-mash
ドッカン！ ケミストーリー
Boom! Chemi-story
曖昧な君を纏うグラフィー
Graphy wrapped around uncertain you
変化形のジェネリック
Transformed generic
もっと夢中になれなせー！
Get even more hooked, okay!
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four!
ぎゅっと射止めたい君の胸！
I want to capture your heart tightly!
爆発的科学反応（クラッシュ）！
Explosive chemical reaction!
爆・爆・君とケミストリー！
Bang, bang, chemistry with you!
疑惑の甘い試薬（エージェント）
Suspicious sweet reagent
解けないドキドキするはず？
It shouldn't dissolve, my heart's supposed to throb, right?
ねぇ？ ひろい脳内ハイウェイ
Hey? The vast highway in my brain
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない！
That's not the kind of throb I meant!
けどまぁ、ある意味成功かな？
But well, in a way, is it a success?
ラブ湧く要素 実験待ち時間
Love-surging elements, waiting time for experiment
試作中 今度はどうでしょう？
Prototype in progress, how about this time?
どこ行く？ そんなクライマックス
Where are you going? Such a climax
反応重ねてくテレパシー
Telepathy repeating reactions
ぎゅっとさませたくて理性のネジ
Wanting to tighten up the screw of reason
願望の目見る君が一番！
You looking with hopeful eyes are number one!
中和剤？ タダですか？
Neutralizer? Is it free?
僕特製のアンチドート！
My special antidote!
ドッカン！ 見せたいな
Boom! I wanna show you
曖昧な君を纏うグラフィー
Graphy wrapped around uncertain you
変化形のジェネリック
Transformed generic
どんな毒も観測してさ！
Observing any poison!
ドッカン！ 君プラス私！
Boom! You plus me!
解けなくてもっとチャレンジャー！
Even if unsolved, be more of a challenger!
君こそが愛のアトミック！
You are the atomic of love!
もっと夢中になれなせー！
Get even more hooked, okay!
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four!
ぎゅっと射止めたい君の胸！
I want to capture your heart tightly!
爆発的科学反応（クラッシュ）！
Explosive chemical reaction!
爆・爆・君とついた検証！
Bang, bang, verification made with you!
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four!
ぎゅっと射止めたい君の胸！
I want to capture your heart tightly!
爆発的科学反応（クラッシュ）！
Explosive chemical reaction!
爆・爆・君とケミストリー！
Bang, bang, chemistry with you!
実験は君と得たり！
The experiment is complete with you!
君が好きってこの感情に潰されてる
Crushed by this feeling of liking you
足りないのはどちらのほうか どうでもいいかも
Which of us falls short, maybe it doesn't matter
気づいていたって知らないよ 責任の逃避
Even if you noticed, you act like you don't know, escaping responsibility
あたしはなんで好きなんだって
Why do I even like you,
問い正す流れ
I ask myself in this endless loop.
最低になったあの子のほうがいいんだもんね
After all, you prefer that girl who hit rock bottom, right?
あたし興味ないよ
I don't care at all
君なんて
about someone like you.
マジ半端ないで
Don't look down on me
舐めた真似
with your half-hearted love.
滑稽渦中のこのハイに
In this high, right in the middle of absurdity,
壊されたい
I want to be destroyed.
はぁ 壊されたい
Ah, I want to be destroyed.
止め処ないよ 君の愛を
Unstoppable, I want to monopolize
独り占めしたい
your love all for myself.
毒だろうが何だろうが
Whether it's poison or whatever,
抱きしめてあげたい
I want to hold it tight.
ライセンス契約
License agreement,
独占のポリグラフ
exclusive polygraph,
逃がさない ずっと
I won't let you escape, ever.
君が好きって この感情に
Saying "I like you"... by this feeling,
騙されてる
I'm being fooled.
大事なほうは 君か私か
Which one is more important, you or me?
決めかねてる
I can't decide.
バカすぎる君へ
To you, who are far too foolish...
あたし興味ないよ
I don't care at all
君なんて
about someone like you.
空回りさせて
Let yourself run in circles,
好きなだけ
as much as you like.
ろくでなしなこの愛を
This good-for-nothing love...
渡さないから
I won't hand it over to you.
バカだよね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
色ボケだね
Blinded by love, aren't you?
それ見たことかだろ
It's a "told you so" situation, isn't it?
もう他で野良
Already straying somewhere else,
あなたに呪われたまま
while remaining cursed by you...
や、興味ないよ
Yeah, I don't care at all
君なんて
about someone like you.
バカなフリしてあげただけ
I just played the fool for you.
愛と愛をぶつけ合って
Clashing love against love,
ぐちゃぐちゃになって
getting all messed up.
あたし興味ないよ
I don't care at all
君なんて
about someone like you.
マジ半端ないで
Don't look down on me
舐めた真似
with your half-hearted love.
滑稽渦中のこの愛に
In this love, right in the middle of absurdity,
壊されたい
I want to be destroyed.
はぁ...
Ah...
はぁ 壊されたい
Ah, I want to be destroyed.
見た目だけじゃ判らない
You can't tell just from appearances,
私のこと「可愛い」と言われても
even if you call me "cute."
まさか思っていないよね
Surely you don't think that, right?
私のホント
The true me...
知っていてほしい
I want you to know.
ホントノワタシ
[Title: The True Me]
予測誤差の範囲と
Saying it's within the margin of prediction error,
不測の事態も
and that unexpected situations
動じない
don't shake you,
お澄ましフェイスでいるけど
keeping a composed face...
心は常に青白く燃え
But inside, my heart burns pale blue constantly.
諦めはしない 媚びたりもしない
I won't give up, nor will I flatter.
私 おまけじゃない
I am not just an extra!
扱いやすい奴と思うな
Don't think I'm someone easy to handle!
甘く見ると 痛い目見るぞ
Take me lightly, and you'll pay the price!
それでも
Even so,
時には 逃げ出してしまいたい
sometimes I just want to run away.
そんな衝動に 弱音吐きたくなる夜もある
Pressed by such impulses, there are nights I want to vent my weaknesses.
ほんの小さな 小さな妥協が
Even a tiny, tiny compromise...
積み重なり 重なって 動けない
Piles up and up until I can't move.
大きな 大きな可能性なくし
Losing grand possibilities,
未来を 狭めてしまうから
it narrows down the future, so...
どんなに暗くても 辛くても 後悔だけはしない
No matter how dark or painful, regret is the one thing I won't do!
生き方を見せる チャレンジャーじゃなくて 生き方なんだ
I'll show you my way of life—I'm not just a challenger, it's my way of living!
現実と理想の 距離を縮められたとしても
Even if I manage to narrow the gap between reality and my ideals,
お澄ましフェイスでいるだけ
if I just keep on maintaining a cool face,
何事もなかったかのように
as if nothing ever happened...
立ち止まりはしない 後戻りもしない
I won't stop, I won't step back,
夢も捨ててない
and I haven't abandoned my dreams!
私らしく... 誇らしく
Being true to myself... and proud!
見た目だけじゃワカラナイ ワタシのこと
You can't tell who I am just from my looks.
可愛いだけと まさか思っていないよね？
You don't just think I'm cute, do you?
ワタシの真実 知っていてほしい
I want you to know the real me.
それでもときには
Even so, at times,
温もりが恋しい
I long for warmth.
そんな感情に流されてしまいそうな
There are late nights where I feel like...
真夜中もある
...being swept away by such emotions.
だけど
But...
こんな甘い甘いことだけ
I don't need the weakness...
求めてしまうような弱さはいらない
...that makes me seek only sweet, gentle things.
苦い苦い経験だって
Because even bitter experiences...
ワタシを強くしてくれるから
...will make me stronger.
これが これが ワタシの 真実
This is, this is the real me.
とても狭い狭い世界の中だけで
I don't want to end up...
終わらせたくはないんだ
...inside such a tiny, narrow world.
広い広い世界の果てまで
I'm going to run through...
駆け抜けて生きてくんだから
...to the ends of the vast world!
どんなに険しくて過酷でも楽しんでやるさ
No matter how harsh or cruel it gets, I'll enjoy it!
イケてるのは見た目じゃなくて 生き方なんだから
Being cool isn't about looks, it's about how you live!
はい 注目
Attention, please!
あれもこれもそれもたぶんタブー
That, this, and that are probably all taboo.
わ わかってんの？
D-Do you get it?
what is 常
What is normal?
ぷーすかぱーすかグチグチ愚痴じゃナンセンス
Whining and complaining all day is nonsense!
わ わかってない！
Y-You don't get it at all!
集まってらっしゃい
"Gather 'round, everyone!"
後悔がベスティ 狭心症キャパシティ ビビリじゃ負けない比じゃない
Regret is my bestie, my capacity's tight, fear is unmatched!
あげる絶句ビンタ
Here's a slap to leave you speechless!
表面上だけalways漂白してもねぇ？
Even if you bleach the surface always, you know?
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけないくらい
So much pain that it won't fly away,
称賛圧巻毛細胞で
with overwhelming praise down to the hair cells,
能ない鷹は爪出しましょう
incompetent hawks, show off your claws!
あたし アナスタシスガール
I'm the Anastasis Girl!
不滅量産型女 (サタン！)
Immortal mass-produced girl (Satan!)
だからなんなんなんなんなん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち二のさんで dun dun dun
On three, dun dun dun!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
昨日イジめた罰 (あはん)
Punishment for yesterday's bullying (Ahan!)
君なんなんなんなんなん
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだんだん
Down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride
Revolution, go ride!
革命 go ride アナスタシスガール
Revolution, go ride, Anastasis Girl!
お口チャック
Zip your mouth,
皆で花一匁
everyone play Hana Ichi Monme.
お口チャック
Zip your mouth,
アタシだけに幸あれ
may happiness come only to me.
健やかなるときも病めるときも
In sickness and in health,
前頭葉人間らしくあれ
let your frontal lobe be human.
どうも美の微調節が不可欠
Fine-tuning beauty is indispensable.
die or die or die or die or die or die or die or die
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけないならば
If the pain won't fly away,
やっっちゃえいっちゃえ精神論で
do it, go for it with sheer willpower!
目には目を致してやりましょう
Let's give them an eye for an eye!
あたし アナスタシスガール
I'm the Anastasis Girl!
ブレイコーのお時間 (サタン！)
Time to let loose and party! (Satan!)
だからなんなんなんなんなん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち二のさんで dun dun dun
On three, dun dun dun!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
極めて遺憾です (あはん)
It's extremely regrettable! (Ahan!)
君なんなんなんなんなん
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだんだん
Down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride
Revolution, go ride!
革命 go ride アナスタシスガール
Revolution, go ride, Anastasis Girl!
あぁ あぁ お願いほっといて
Ah, ah, please leave me alone.
とびきりの嘘と嘘が飛び散った Tシャツ
A T-shirt splattered with supreme lies upon lies.
汚れと慣れの果てが生み出した ドンギブアップ
"Don't give up" born from the depths of dirt and habit.
あたし アナスタシスガール
I'm the Anastasis Girl!
不滅量産型女 (サタン！)
Immortal mass-produced girl (Satan!)
だからなんなんなんなんなん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち二のさんで dun dun dun
On three, dun dun dun!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
昨日イジめた罰 (あはん)
Punishment for yesterday's bullying (Ahan!)
君なんなんなんなんなん
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだんだん
Down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride
Revolution, go ride!
革命 go ride アナスタシスガール
Revolution, go ride, Anastasis Girl!
スキじゃない スキじゃない
Not love, not love
ラブのリポート 冷めやらぬ感情
Love report, feelings that won't cool down
バカじゃないの 目を覚まして
Are you stupid? Wake up!
ねぇ？
Hey?
全然平常心で
Staying completely calm,
興味とか心酔だらけ
full of interest and infatuation,
戯けだしてウォンチュー
fooling around, wanting you
自覚できなくて困る
It's troubling not being aware of it
Listen, baby
たまに構ってあげる
I'll pay attention to you once in a while
癖になっちまう
It's becoming a habit
絶妙な距離感
An exquisite sense of distance
ゲーム 近づく
Game, getting closer
一生デカく デカく デカく デカく
Forever bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger
なんでも頂戴サイズ
Give me any size
絶好のスキ作りましょう
Let's create the perfect love
それがライクなのかラブなのか
Is that like or is that love?
はたまた両方なのでは？
Or perhaps both?
なし！ あり！ なし！ 絶対あるだろ！
No! Yes! No! There definitely is!
そしてデカく デカく デカく デカく
And bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger
とにかくデカく
Anyway, bigger
いいよ 全部叶うからね
It's fine, because everything will come true
結局思い通りないと
If it's not as expected in the end,
ノラないノラないわ
I won't join in, won't join in
大賛成やっていきましょう
Full agreement, let's do this!
あんたのスキは
Your love is...
デカく スキデカく
Big, love is big
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
沢山の感情 みんなに伝えて♡
Express so many emotions to everyone...
俺だけに魅せてくれたっていいのぜ いいのぜ
It's fine to show it only to me, totally fine!
一人特別 サービス出来ません
I can't give special treatment to just one person
それでもいいのかな？
Is that still okay?
もっと知りたいことだらけ
So many things I want to know more about
程々にして
Keep it in moderation
でも知らない方が幸せか
But maybe ignorance is bliss?
お時間にしてよね
Give it some time, okay?
絶妙な距離感 ゲーム バランスを取り合う
Exquisite sense of distance, a game of keeping balance
一生つかず離れず
Never too close, never too far apart forever
つらいかな？
Is it painful?
丁度いい塩梅で
Just the right balance
お互いもっと分かり合えたら
If we could understand each other more
特別になれる？
Can we become special?
いつも通じ合える
Always understanding each other
この先は想像できないけど
I can't imagine what lies ahead, but
結構いい感じかも
It might feel pretty good
ギリギリでもいい感じ
Even on the edge, it feels good
そのまま進みます
Continuing forward as is
踏み付けて行きます
Treading forward
ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたい
I want to discuss our future right here
ホント要らないでしょ！ いいからほら！
We really don't need to! Come on, hurry!
3 2 1 Let's go!
一生フレンズがふたり
Two friends forever
一生デカく デカく デカく デカく
Forever bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger
何でも頂戴サイズ
Give me any size
絶好のスキ作りましょう
Let's create the perfect love
それがライクなのかラブなのか
Is that like or is that love?
はたまた両方なのでは？
Or perhaps both?
なし！ あり！ なし！ 絶対あるだろ！
No! Yes! No! There definitely is!
そしてデカく デカく デカく デカく
And bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger
とにかくデカく
Anyway, bigger
いいよ 全部叶うからね
It's fine, because everything will come true
結局思い通りないと
If it's not as expected in the end,
ノラないノラないわ
I won't join in, won't join in
大賛成やっていきましょう
Full agreement, let me do this!
一生つかず離れず
Never too close, never too far apart forever
飽きられず
Without getting bored of each other
ちょうどいい塩梅で
Just the right balance
お前ともっと
With you, even more
くだらないことでもワイワイしていたい
I want to have fun even over silly things
つついていたい
I want to tease you
この先も変わらない関係性を
A relationship that won't change in the future
ちょっと行き過ぎて
Going a bit too far
まだちょっと前進後退 一旦まず進みます
Still moving forward and backward, for now let's just move forward
３歩進んで戻ります！
Move three steps forward and step back!
スキはデカく スキデカく
Love is big, love is big
しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Please bear with me for a while longer
不思議な関係 お見知りおきを
A mysterious relationship, pleased to make your acquaintance!
超現象フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon
東奔西走タイムレス
Busily running east and west, timeless
ネオ・レッドガー ほら最強ジャン
Neo Red Guard, look, it's the strongest!
いま焼き付けろ
Burn it in right now
超現象フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon
東奔西走タイムレス
Busily running east and west, timeless
閃光探偵 閃光探偵
Flash detective, flash detective
さあ ババババババン
Now, ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-bang!
満月の夜 くぐり抜けて
Slinking through the night of the full moon
ビルの間まで ため息…
Deep sigh between the skyscrapers...
本性のルーペで 探し出して
Search it out with the magnifying glass of true nature
深い闇へ 誘うの
Inviting you into the deep darkness
大胆不敵 秘密の正体
Daring and fearless, a secret identity
逃げていく世界を制せよ
Conquer the escaping world
オレンジに染まっていく崩壊
Collapse dyeing everything in orange
君のためにメラメラ
Burning brightly for your sake
愛を燃やしてメラメラ
Burning love brightly
守り抜くと誓った あの日から
From that day I swore to protect till the end
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning brightly for tomorrow
この波に乗っちゃえば
If you ride this wave
退屈なんて縁でしょ さようなら
Boredom has no place here, goodbye!
超現象フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon
東奔西走タイムレス
Busily running east and west, timeless
ネオ・レッドガー ほら最強ジャン
Neo Red Guard, look, it's the strongest!
いま焼き付けろ
Burn it in right now
超現象フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon
東奔西走タイムレス
Busily running east and west, timeless
Don't stop the shining, don't cry, don't cry...
変化 コンプラ 迷彩 カメレオン
Change, compliance, camouflage, chameleon
超常現象 ちょうだい チョコレート
Paranormal phenomenon, give me chocolate
警察 盗賊 爆音 警笛
Police, thieves, roaring sirens
夢のためにメラメラ 闇を燃やすメラメラ
Blazing for our dreams, blazing as we burn through darkness
どんな時もこの声は 届けたい
No matter when, I want this voice to reach you
崖っぷちでメラメラ 諦めるには早いわ
Blazing at the edge of the cliff, it's too early to give up
恩返し 奇跡を起こしましょ
Let's repay the favor and make miracles happen
勝負師 セレブ 探求 綺麗な天然記念物
Gambler, celebrity, seeker, beautiful natural monument
秘密結社は意外？ 障害だってお構いなし
Is a secret society unexpected? Obstacles won't bother us
どこにいたって迷子になっちゃってもプンプンデス
Wherever I am, even if I get lost, I'm super pouting
有象無象で揉んで巻いて
Swirling through the chaotic crowd
電光石火 ESCAPE
Lightning speed, ESCAPE
君のためにメラメラ 愛を燃やすメラメラ
Blazing for you, blazing as we burn with love
守りぬくと誓ったあの日から
Ever since that day I swore to protect you
明日のためにメラメラ この音に乗って EVER
Blazing for tomorrow, riding on this sound EVER
退屈なんて無縁でしょ さようなら
Boredom has nothing to do with us, farewell
超常現象 RESONANCE 東奔西走 TIME TO RED
Paranormal phenomenon RESONANCE, running east and west, TIME TO RED
RED or BLACK 叫び続けろ
RED or BLACK, keep shouting
超常現象 RESONANCE 東奔西走 TIME TO RED
Paranormal phenomenon RESONANCE, running east and west, TIME TO RED
揉んで揉んで
Mix it, mix it
BAN BAN BAN BAN BAN
ねぇねぇねぇねぇ！ルイ姉さ、めっちゃ勝ってたよね！
Hey, hey, hey! Lui-nee, you were totally winning, right?
めっちゃ勝ってたね！めっちゃ楽しかったね！
She totally was! That was so much fun!
めっちゃかっこよかった！めっちゃいいよね！
You looked so cool! That was awesome!
まだ終わってないからね！これからが最高だよね！
It's not over yet! The best is yet to come, right?
なんやこれ？
What's this?
あ、気づいちゃいました？
Ah, did you notice?
変じゃない？めっちゃかっこいいじゃん！
Isn't it cool? It looks super cool!
こよりが作りました！
Koyori made this!
また研究費使ったんか！
You used the research budget again?!
これが吾輩らの給料...！いやいや、みんなの給料同じだからね！
Is this where our salary went?! No no, everyone's salary is the same!
おかしいよな！
That's strange, right?!
ということで、これは告知用カード！
So, these are announcement cards!
おー！
Oh!
なんだこれ？あ、告知！
What's this? Ah, announcement!
ということで、この流れでね、グッズ紹介でございますね！
And with that, following this flow, it's time for merchandise introduction!
今回はそういう感じね！
So that's how it is this time!
はい、じゃあ私からね、いきますよ！
Alright, then I'll start, here we go!
はい、holoX活動4周年記念グッズ！
Okay, holoX 4th Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade、今日の18時より販売開始されております！
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade goes on sale starting today at 6:00 PM!
それでは、それぞれ見ていきましょう！
Now then, let's take a look at each of them!
まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙、ドーン！
First, the Premium Acrylic Shikishi, boom!
イエーイ！今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です！
Yay! It's an acrylic shikishi featuring this time's key visual!
なんと、複製サインとロゴが箔押しになってて、めっちゃいい感じじゃない！
Look, the replicated signatures and logo are foil-stamped, isn't that awesome!
かっこいい！かっこいい！
Cool! Cool!
そしてお次がこちら、ホロマスリーブ！
And next is this, Holoca Sleeves!
このカードがまさにそれなんですけど！
This card is exactly that!
キービジュアルを使ったホロカスリーブです！
These are Holoca Sleeves using the key visual!
こちらなんと、60枚入り！
And these actually come in a pack of 60!
わー！やったー！何個あってもいいですからね！
Wow! Yay! You can never have too many!
ホロカに使いやすいですね！
They're super handy for Holoca!
そして！
And next!
アクリルスタンドー！
Acrylic Stands!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、
They feature different facial expressions from the key visual design,
ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいね！
so please compare them with the acrylic shikishi!
キモい！帰ってきた！
Creepy! She came back!
えー、こよりとね、いろはもね、可愛いね！可愛い可愛い！
Ah, Koyori and Iroha are cute too! So cute, so cute!
そして、こちら！
And here's this!
はい、記念メダルも発売しております！
Yes, Commemorative Medals are also on sale!
なんとね、ケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます！
These commemorative medals actually come with a case and a drawstring pouch!
こちらね、期ごとにデザインが異なっておりますので、
The design differs depending on the generation,
なんと今回はholoXだけのデザインになっております！
so this time it features a design exclusive to holoX!
ぜひぜひゲットして、よくチェックしてみてくださいね！
Be sure to get yours and check it out!
なんか騒がしいな！
It's pretty noisy!
はい！ということで、次は何のカイドー？
Alright! So, what's the next card?
カードーちゃん！2枚目、オープン！
Card-chan! Second one, open!
あるのね！ということで、タイミーコラボ！
Oh, there is one! So, it's the Timee collaboration!
タイミーだ！タイミーさんやってましたね！
It's Timee! Timee was doing this, right!
先日のタイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど、
Regarding the rare part-time jobs recruited on Timee recently,
現地の様子があるということで、
we have footage from the actual location!
見てみましょう！ドン！
Let's check it out! Boom!
おー！すごーい！
Woah! Awesome!
ちゃんとholoX服着てる！
They're properly wearing holoX outfits!
すごい！配ってくれてる！ありがとうみんな！
Amazing! They're handing them out! Thank you, everyone!
他の配っているのもありますよ！ドン！
We have other distribution clips too! Boom!
なるよね
It really does.
でもこれで知ってくれた人もいるよね、たぶん
But maybe there are people who learned about us from this too.
ねー、絶対そう！ うれしい！
Right? Absolutely! I'm so glad!
もう1枚あります！ ドン！
There's one more! Bam!
おー！ え、新宿？ あ、後ろにも映ってる！
Oh! Wait, Shinjuku? Ah, it's showing in the back too!
あれ？ あれ？ 消えた？ 嘘でしょ？！ 聞いてないよ！
Wait, what? Did it vanish? You've got to be kidding! Nobody told us!
待って、今日の21時前に流れていたあの良く分からないやつ？
Wait, was that that weird mystery clip that aired before 21:00 today?
おい！ 流れてたのかよ！ 大丈夫か？
Hey! So it was playing?! Is this okay?
もっとさ、なんかかっこいいMVとか、ライブ映像とか流したら...
If you were gonna show something, why not cool MVs or live footage?
ほんとだよ！ でもありがとう！ やったー！
Seriously! But thank you! Yay!
と言うことでこちら、応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
So, for this... how many applications do you think we got?
でも平日の昼間だからね、100人とか来てくれたら...
But it was a weekday daytime, right? If even 100 people showed up...
平日の真っ昼間だからね。なんと！
Right in the middle of a weekday. And the result is...
数千人の応募が来たということです！
We received applications from several thousand people!
すごすぎる！ ありがとう！ 恐ろしいよ！
That's amazing! Thank you so much! That's insane!
そんなに？！ ちょっと給料もらったせいだ！
That many?! Is it because they paid salaries?!
給料もらったせい？ もらってるに決まってるでしょ！
Because they got paid? Of course they get paid!
いろはより多めに渡してます。やめて！
I paid them more than I pay Iroha. Stop that!
ありがとうございます！ 参加してくれた皆さんもありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thanks to everyone who participated too!
そして、次はなんだ？ オープン！
And what's next? Open!
来ました！ じゃじゃーん！ タワーコラボだー！
Here it comes! Ta-da! It's a Tower Collaboration!
タワーコラボ、もう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
Information for the tower collab has already been released, but here it is!
全国4箇所で行われる『秘密結社holoX Tower Invasion』！
"Secret Society holoX Tower Invasion", taking place at 4 locations nationwide!
さっぽろテレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力 MIRAI TOWER、梅田スカイビルで開催されます！
It'll be held at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER, and Umeda Sky Building!
俺たちがタワーだ！ おい、待て待て！
We are the towers! Hey, wait, wait!
今回大事なことがあるんですけど、ちゃんと予約しないと入れないんで事前予約必須です！
There's an important detail this time: you can't get in without a reservation, so advance booking is required!
そう、事前予約を忘れてる人もいると思うので。その場で行っても入れないらしいんで。
Right, some people might forget to book in advance. Apparently you can't enter on the spot.
ちゃんと予約忘れないように！ よろしくお願いしますよ！
Make sure not to forget your reservation! Please keep that in mind!
よろしくね！ 次！ 次！
Please do! Next! Next!
オープン！ はい！
Open! Yes!
なんと！ ホロライブの新しいサービス！ ライブの感動を最速で手元に！
What?! A new Hololive service! Bring the live excitement to your hands faster than ever!
おー、すごい！ どういうことだ？
Oh, awesome! What does that mean?
秘密結社holoX 4周年のライブブロマイドが！ 今日のライブの写真が明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだって！
Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary Live Bromides! Photos from today's live can be printed out at convenience stores starting tomorrow!
手に入るんだ！ 対象店舗はファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります！
You can get them! Target stores are FamilyMart, Lawson, and MiniStop!
イェーイ！ いっぱいある！ ありがとうございます！
Yay! There are so many! Thank you so much!
そして、今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです！ マジで？
And apparently you can pre-purchase them online starting right now! Seriously?
明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので、詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
Starting tomorrow you can also choose and buy photos at convenience stores, so check the link on the bottom left for details!
こっちこっち！ さらにですね、今回はそちらのお写真に、ブロマイドに...
Over here! Furthermore, this time, on those photos, on the bromides...
私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけれども... 今から書くんです！
It seems we can attach our own handwritten messages... and we're going to write them right now!
ここで？！ 尺足りなくない？ 何も考えてないけど...
Right here?! Won't we run out of time? I haven't thought of anything though...
何に... どうなるの？ 考えて書いてください！
What... what's gonna happen? Think of something and write it!
え、書いて... なにこれ...
Wait, writing... what is this...
時間も迫ってますからね、早く書きましょう。意外と集中力... つなげ！
Time is running out, so let's write quickly. They're surprisingly focused... Someone stall!
安牌で！ 出来たー！ 早くない？
Play it safe! Done! Isn't that too fast?
見せて。こよっぽいね。いつまで書いてんの？
Show me. That's very Koyo-like. How long are you gonna take writing?
みんな終わった？ これでみんな渡して！
Is everyone done? Pass them over, everyone!
ということで、みんなが何を書いたかすごく気になると思うんですが...
So, I'm sure everyone is really curious about what everyone wrote, but...
メッセージの内容は... みんなが買ってからのお楽しみ！
The content of the messages... is a surprise for after you buy them!
言わないで！ ダメに決まってんだろ！ あ、ごめんなさい！
Don't say it! Of course you can't! Ah, sorry!
はい！ そして... まだ2枚あるんで、お次はこちら！
Yes! And... we still have two cards left, so next is this!
オープン！ 告知⑤『あの作品とコラボ！？』
Open! Announcement #5: "A collaboration with THAT series?!"
なんと、あの作品とコラボ？！ え？ 何々？
What?! A collaboration with THAT series?! Eh? What's this?
ちょっと待って、これはマジで知らない... あの作品って何ですか？ こちらをどうぞ！
Wait a second, I genuinely don't know about this... What series is "THAT series"? Take a look at this!
サテーー 突然デハアルガ、或ル秘密結社ノ 話ヲシヨウ。人間ハ、
Now then... It may be sudden, but let us speak of a certain secret society. Humans are...
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That mysterious group...
偶像――“アキドル” ナノダト云フ。
...is said to be idols.
ソシテー―
And...
正確ナ話ヲスルト 征服ショウトシテイルノハ エデンノ星ラシイ。
To be precise, what they seek to conquer is Planet Eden.
タダ、ドゥイウコトカ、 交ハルハズノナキ世界ガ、 今回バカリハ 油断シテシマッタラシイ。
However, two worlds that should never cross have let their guard down just this once.
交 kou. (2021)
Cross
特別話 秘密結社 holoX × 物語シリーズ 其ノ零
Special Episode: Secret Society holoX x Monogatari Series - Episode Zero
〈物語〉シリーズ × holoX コラボ開催決定
Monogatari Series x holoX Collaboration Confirmed!
えー！？ええー！？いいの！？え、やばい！
Eh?! Really?! Is this for real?!
え、マジ？え、めちゃ大好きじゃんね？ね、好き！え、やばすぎる！
Seriously?! Wait, isn't someone here a huge fan?! Yeah, I love it! This is insane!
え、どういうこと？どっか行っちゃう！どこか行っちゃう！
Wait, what does this mean? Wait, where are you going?!
え、ちょっと待って！ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Wait a second! Thank you so much!
なんと！え、マジで？怒られない？吾輩。怒られない、吾輩？
What?! Really?! Are we gonna get scolded for this?!
怒られるとしたら、台本を読んでない吾輩が… 早く言え！
If anyone gets scolded, it'll be me for not reading the script! Say it faster!
なんと「物語シリーズ」とのコラボが決定しました！
Believe it or not, a collaboration with the Monogatari series has been confirmed!
やったー！みんなも言ってる！
Yay! Look, everyone in chat is saying it too!
詳細は随時発表されるようなので… 我々も分かっていない！
Details will be announced gradually, so... Even we don't know yet!
そうなんです！本当に詳細何も分かってない…
That's right! We genuinely don't know any details...
どうなるんでしょうか？うちらもちょっと焦ってるんですけど…
What's going to happen? We're actually a bit flustered ourselves...
いいんですか？っていう感じなんですけれども…
We're like, "Is this really okay?" But...
最後にひとつ、あるみたいなのでそちらに行きましょう。
It seems there's one last thing, so let me move on to that.
あ、もういっこ！もういっこ見ないと！一旦動揺を…落ち着けてみんな。
Ah, there's one more! We have to check one more! Everyone, calm down a bit.
我々が動揺してる間に…皆さん、この6つ目が何かコメントで教えてみてください！
While we're flustered... Everyone, try guessing what this 6th one is in the comments!
何かな？予想してみてね！
What could it be? Give us your predictions!
忍？忍じゃないかな？何のことで？
Shinobu? Could it be Shinobu?
最後のひとつは皆さん何だと思いますか？
What do you all think the final announcement is?
なんとですね…ヒントを言うと…
Surprisingly... To give you a hint...
今年2曲作りましたよね？全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
We made 2 songs this year, right? How many songs does holoX have in total?
何曲？たくさん！覚えてないのか？
How many? A lot! Wait, you don't remember?!
holoXで出してきた企画曲を除きますと…全部で7曲あります！
Excluding special event songs, holoX has 7 songs in total!
7曲！すごい！
7 songs! Amazing!
てことは…？惜しい？コメント欄分かってきたんじゃない？
Which means...? Is anyone close? Looks like the comments are figuring it out!
気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、やっぱりあちらでございます！6枚目、オープン！
Some people seem to have noticed! So here it is! Card number six, open!
なんと！1stアルバムが出ます！
What?! Our 1st Album is coming out!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
ということで、1stアルバム「Secret ORDER」！
So there you have it, our 1st Album, "Secret ORDER"!
「Secret ORDER」！みんな知ってたよー！
"Secret ORDER"! Everyone already knew!
こちらの「Secret ORDER」、holoXでの4年間をぎゅっと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
This "Secret ORDER" album is packed with our 4 years of holoX!
我々のデビュー曲「オーロラ・ペイント」はオリジナル版に加えて、本作のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
In addition to the original version, our debut song "JOYFUL PAINT" features a newly rearranged version created just for this album!
そしてさらに！未発表の楽曲も…？
And on top of that... There are also unreleased songs?!
え、何曲あるの？！10曲とか11曲とか？！ヤバすぎる！
Wait, how many songs are there?! Like 10 or 11?! That's insane!
ということでですね、通常盤になるんですけれども…上が見えないで！
So, regarding the standard edition... Hey, don't block the screen!
通常盤には初回限定特典があります！
The standard edition comes with a first-press limited bonus!
こちらでございますね。各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット4種類のうちランダムで1枚つきます！
Here it is. It includes 1 random solo jacket out of 4 member solo versions!
そしてこちらですね、4枚並べると…どうやら1枚絵になるとのことですよ！
And if you line up these 4 cards... Apparently, they form one complete illustration!
すごい！つながりそう！ラプラスの角が刀の上にある！本当だ！
Woah, look at that! Laplus's horn is right above the sword! It really is!
これさ、並べないと見えないね！
You really have to line them up to see it!
そして、完全生産限定盤封入特典は…
And as for the Complete Limited Edition bonus...
カッコよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが…？
This super cool album contains a secret holoX gimmick...?
え？！吾輩達も分かってないぞ！隠されているとか…？
What?! Even we don't know about this! Something hidden...?
私たちも分からないのですが、この後22時から販売開始です！
We don't even know ourselves, but pre-orders start tonight at 22:00!
ぜひぜひご予約お願いいたします！お願いします！
Please make sure to pre-order it!
ということで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけれども…
So, we had a whole lot of announcements...
告知カードちゃんたちはこれで役目が終わり…消えろー！
The announcement cards have finished their job... Begone!
消えたー！すごい！
They disappeared! Amazing!
ギミックやばいなこれ！消すのだけ上手い！
That gimmick is crazy! You're only good at making them disappear!
ということで、ライブもラストスパートでございます。
And with that, our live stream is entering its final stretch.
この後ですね、なにやらちょっとお知ら…サプライズがあるらしいですよ？
After this, it seems there's some kind of... surprise announcement?
最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いいたします！
Please stay tuned until the very end!
それじゃあみんな、最後まで楽しんでね！
Alright everyone, enjoy until the end!
行くぞー！イエーイ！
Let me hear you! Yeah!
おい！おい！おい！
Oi! Oi! Oi!
そこに膝跪いて 伏して平伏せよ
Kneel before me, prostrate yourselves!
現実を一刀両断 叩き斬れ
Cut through reality with a single stroke!
終わり無き輪廻に迷いし古来より
Wandering through the endless cycle of reincarnation,
漆黒の翼で誘おう
guided by wings of jet black...
我ら エデンの星を統べる者
We are the rulers of the star of Eden,
秘密結社...
Secret Society...
HoloX!
でござる！
...de gozaru!
Wo-oh, wo-oh...
反応 How now? どうしようもないこの世界
How now? What to do in this hopeless world?
どうしてほしい？
What do you want us to do?
馬鹿
Fool.
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell tolling the end chimes.
陰キャも陽キャも sing a song
Introverts and extroverts alike, sing a song!
気持ちいいことだけが全て 堕ちてゆく闇の底へ
Only feeling good is everything, falling into the dark depths.
甘い甘いメロディ ほらどうぞどうぞ手の鳴る方へ
Sweet, sweet melody, come this way to the clapping hands.
もう人間になれない
You can't be human anymore!
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
if you're dyed in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めば狂えてやろう
If you wish, we'll go crazy for you.
すべて常識破り捨てろ
Tear up and discard all common sense!
狂狂狂い倒せ 気を付けろ
Go mad, mad, completely mad, watch out!
すべてを暗転させ
Plunge everything into darkness!
秘密を教えてやろう
We'll teach you our secret!
Wo-oh, wo-oh...
悪のカリスマ 導くぞため息さ 正義とか知らない 地ならししていざない
The charisma of evil will guide you with a sigh, ignorant of justice, flattening the earth and inviting you.
真面目に不真面目 電車の津々浦々 望み求め願い叶え 世界征服
Seriously lighthearted everywhere on the train, seeking desires, granting wishes, world conquest!
褪せることのない夢を見せる
We'll show you a dream that never fades.
ほら お眠りなさい
Come, go to sleep.
もっともっと遠くへ ほらどうぞどうぞ行きたいでしょう
Further, even further away, come on, you want to go, don't you?
もうやめられない
You can't stop anymore!
ほら
Look,
悪に染まれば
if you're dyed in evil...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望むものを与えよう
We'll give you what you desire.
すべてルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite all the rules!
狂狂回し尽くせ 突き尽くせ
Spin, spin around completely, thrust all the way!
すべてを紛い物へ
Turn everything into an imitation!
秘密を教えてやろう
We'll teach you our secret!
ついに4周年！
Finally, our 4th anniversary!
狂気の宴の始まりだ！
The mad banquet begins!
貴様ら 準備はいいか！
Are you bastards ready?!
刮目せよ！
Pay close attention!
HoloX! HoloX! Laplus! Laplus! Iroha! Iroha!
叫ぶでござる！
Shout it out!
Koyori! Koyori! 踊れ！踊れ！
Koyori! Koyori! Dance! Dance!
世界を手にする HoloX! 世界を変えてく HoloX!
HoloX taking over the world! HoloX changing the world!
Lui-nee! Lui-nee! もっと！もっと！
Lui-nee! Lui-nee! More! More!
Love Lu-Knight! Love Lu-Knight!
最後は全員でー！
Lastly, everybody together!
HoloX! HoloX! 世界を手にする HoloX! 世界を変えてく HoloX! 世界をこの手に HoloX!
HoloX! HoloX! HoloX taking over the world! HoloX changing the world! HoloX with the world in our hands!
心を解き放ち
Unleash your heart,
ほらどうぞどうぞ身を任せて
here, go ahead, entrust yourself to us.
もう逃げられない
You can no longer escape!
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
if you're dyed in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めば狂えてやろう
If you wish, we'll go crazy for you.
すべて常識破り捨てろ
Tear up and discard all common sense!
狂狂狂い倒せ 気を付けろ
Go mad, mad, completely mad, watch out!
すべてを暗転させ
Plunge everything into darkness!
秘密を教えてやろう
We'll teach you our secret!
Wo-oh, wo-oh...
「我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…」
[Text: "We are the rulers of the star of Eden, Secret Society..."]
我らエデンの星を統べる者 秘密結社...
We who rule the star of Eden... Secret society...
holoX!
で、ござる～！
De gozaru~!
機は熟した！ 暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ、準備はいかが！！
The time has ripened! Heroic spirits born from the darkness, are you ready?!
お～～～！！！
Ohhh!!!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
Night deepens, look, darkness.
能ある鷹はPONで隠す
A wise hawk hides its claws under 'PON'.
脳に従えエゴイスティック
Follow your instincts, egoistic.
のっと！ニンニン サムライGirl
Not a ninja! Samurai Girl.
闇金しないけど フルベットでしょ
No loan sharking, but it's a full bet, right?
征服すればall right 切り裂く赤字
If we conquer it's all right, cutting through the red ink.
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
In the palm of evil, making you want to dance.
ほら君も 気付けば ノリノリです
Look, before you know it, you're grooving along.
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine 堕ちてく運命
Helpless, Don't show, No mine, a falling fate.
ならしょうがない もう全部 塗り替えよう
Then it can't be helped, let's repaint everything now.
Xと Xと Xと Xが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect right in the center.
Nextと Nextと Nextと 世界はもう 始まってる
Next and Next and Next, the world has already begun.
トビナ トビナ 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump, jump, toward where the darkness calls.
暗黒の エクステス
Darkness Exodus.
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！皆の者、かかれ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in our holoX colors! Everyone, attack!
Yes My Dark!!!
完璧漆黒∞＜アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ＞
Perfect Pitch Black ∞
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホーークアイ！
Demon Eye Hawkeye!
お前もholoXerの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of the holoXers!
カヤリニウム爆パーーん！
Koyarinium Explosion!
これで君も カヤリメイトだー！
Now you are a Koyarmate too!
疾風木ノ葉斬り！
Gale Leaf Slash!
一刀両断 叩き斬る！
Slicing in two with one stroke, strike down!
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine 堕ちてく運命
Helpless, Don't show, No mine, a falling fate.
ならしょうがない もう全部 塗り替えよう
Then it can't be helped, let's repaint everything now.
刮目せよ！！
Pay attention!!
Xと Xと Xと Xが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect right in the center.
Nextと Nextと Nextと 世界はもう 始まってる
Next and Next and Next, the world has already begun.
コビナ コビナ
Flatter, flatter,
つまり最大級
in short, the ultimate.
笑うのは
The ones who laugh...
holoXです
...are holoX.
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
秘密結社holoX 一件の通知
[Secret Society holoX: 1 Notification]
機ハ熟シター―
[The time is ripe—]
全テノ "holoXer" ヘ告グ――
[Notice to all "holoXers"—]
集ヘ、決戦ノ地――
[Gather at the battleground—]
2026.4.29
PIA ARENA MM
秘密結社 holoX Live 2026 FIRST MISSION
[Secret Society holoX Live 2026 FIRST MISSION]
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
[Are you ready to take over the world?]
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
[The mad feast begins!]
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
[#SSholoXWorldRepaintPlan]
やったー！ やっほー！
Yay! Woohoo!
やったー！
We did it!
みんなも驚いてくれてる！
Everyone's so surprised too!
いかがでしたか？
How was that?
ヤバいね！
That's crazy!
まだ早いからね！
It's still early though!
ヤバいね！
That's crazy!
ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
So, our real-life concert has been officially confirmed!
やったー！ ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
ファーストミッション！ やっほー！
FIRST MISSION! Woohoo!
ということでね、みんなそれぞれね、感想と、ライブに向けて抱負をお願いしたいと思います！
So with that, I'd like everyone to share their thoughts and aspirations for the concert!
まずは、じゃあ私から
First, I'll go first.
はい！
Okay!
決まったな！
It's really happening!
いや、めちゃくちゃね、デビューの時から
Ever since our debut,
「ライブやりたいね」って言ってて、デビュー前から
we've been saying, "We want to do a live show," even before debut.
それが、もうありがたいことにね
And now, thankfully...
みんなの協力のおかげで、holoXerさんたちの応援のおかげで
Thanks to everyone's help and all the holoXers' support,
叶いました！やったー！
it came true! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
もう、holoXの...みんなで当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので
All of holoX will make the live super exciting on the day,
ぜひみんな、遊びに来てください！
so please come see us!
かっこいいholoXを見に来てね！
Come see cool holoX!
見に来てね！
Come see us!
ということで、続いては、じゃあこよ！
Alright, next up is Koyori!
はい！
Yes!
今言ってた通り、みんなライブやりたいねって話もしてたし
Like she said, we always talked about wanting to do a live show,
やっぱこよは一番忘れられない風景が、初めてのフェスでholoXでやって...
and for me, the most unforgettable sight was performing as holoX at our first fest...
あの「Joy Paint」で会場がもう「わー！」ってなってくれたの、浴びたとき
and feeling the room go wild when we did "Joy Paint."
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで
I'll never forget that,
やっぱり今度はね、holoXerさんたちだけの...
so this time, a venue just for holoXers...
俺たちの会場で！
Our very own venue!
やれるのはね、めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
Being able to do a show there makes me so happy!
そして、やらせてくれることにさせてくれた大人のみなさんにも...
And to all the staff who made this possible for us...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
この4人の持てる力を全て出して、歌とダンスもより一層力を込めて...
The four of us will give it everything we've got, putting even more power into our singing and dancing...
いきますので！
So get ready!
絶対現地、そして来れない人は映像でも絶対見に来てください！
Whether in person or online, please come watch us!
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
はい！いろは殿！
Alright! Iroha-dono!
はい！
Yes!
みんなー！
Everyone!
生のござるたちの声が聞ける機会！
A chance to hear our live voices!
holoXのこのハーモニーが聞ける機会！
A chance to hear holoX's harmony!
俺たちの共鳴が聞ける！
You can hear our resonance!
本当にね、holoXやっぱ、デビュー前からね
Just like everyone said, ever since before debut,
現地ライブをこのメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので
we always wanted to do an in-person live show together.
それがやっと叶ってね、デカイ声出してみんなで盛り上がれるのをね
Now that dream is coming true, and being able to shout and hype everyone up...
今か今かとね、楽しみにしております！
I can't wait for it!
我々もね、4人ともしっかり当日までレッスンや練習も含め
All four of us will work hard on lessons and practice until the day,
パフォーマンスも全部色々みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて、挑みますので！
thinking of lots of ways to make the performance fun for everyone!
見ている皆さんもぜひ、全力で楽しみにして、そして当日は楽しんでください！
Everyone watching, look forward to it with all your heart, and have fun on the day!
頑張ります！盛り上げる準備、できてます！
We'll do our best! We're ready to pump up the crowd!
できてるぞー！
We're ready!
じゃあ最後！総帥！総帥決めてくれ！
Alright, last up! Leader, wrap it up for us!
吾輩、毎回この最後なのやめてほしいんだよね...
I really wish you wouldn't leave me for last every time...
ちょっとーみんな、ついに... holoXが... 俺たちが... ライブ！
Hey everyone... finally... holoX... we're having a live show!
もうみんなさ、すごいライブやりたい、音楽大好きみたいなのずっと聞いてたからさ
Seeing how much everyone wanted to do a live and loved music all this time...
俺は嬉しいよ！
I'm so happy!
いや、もちろん吾輩も...やっぱりライブが一番楽しいから！
I mean, of course I am too... live shows are the most fun!
やっぱholoXの活動って、なんかライブって感じじゃん？
After all, holoX's activities feel like a live performance, right?
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもholoXerがバーッている所でできるのが嬉しいよな！
So being able to do it with just us, in front of a hall filled with holoXers, makes me so glad!
急に感情が熱いやん！
You got so passionate all of a sudden!
本当に色々あったけど、これからも本当に4人いれば大丈夫だから！頑張ろう！
We've been through a lot, but as long as the four of us are together, we'll be fine! Let's do this!
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
一致団結してさ！
Let's unite!
頑張るぞー！
We're gonna do our best!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
速報です！トレンド1位ということで...
Breaking news! We're #1 on trending!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much everyone!
ここから4月29日までもう止まらねぇぞで、コメントに出まくっててください！
From now until April 29th, there's no stopping us, so flood the comments section!
はい！ということで改めまして、秘密結社holoX 1st Live "First Mission" は...
Alright! So once again, Secret Society holoX 1st Live "First Mission"...
4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
will be held on April 29th at Pia Arena MM!
開けとけ開けとけ！開けといて！
Keep your schedules open!
諸々の詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので、みなさん続報を待てでございます！
Further details will be announced at a later date, so please stay tuned!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
そして、先ほど聴いていただきました新曲...
And the new song you just heard...
「共闇X」です！
is "Kyouan X"!
22時10分よりですね MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
At 22:10, we will premiere our music video!
イエー！ / おー！ / おしゃれですね
Yay! / Woah! / It's so stylish!
かっこいいね！
It's so cool!
えー、本日24時ですね 12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので
Also, today at 24:00—meaning midnight on December 2nd—the digital release will start!
ライブに向けて たくさん聴いてくれよな！
So make sure to listen to it a lot in preparation for the concert!
コールできるところいっぱいあるからね！ / 聴くんだ！
Yeah, there are so many parts where you can do calls! / So listen up!
お前ら新曲聴いて...
Listen to our new song...
お前ら新曲いっぱい聴いて 予習して ライブ楽しみに待っててほしい！
Listen to our new song a lot, prepare, and look forward to the live concert!
そしてアルバム『Secret Order』を 持って...
And also, get our album "Secret Order"...
忘れないように気をつけてね！ / 持って！ / 持って！
Make sure you don't forget to get it! / Get it! / Get it!
ライブ来てね！ 宝物を持ってきてね！ 聴いて予習してね！
Come to the live! Bring your treasures! Listen to it and prepare!
アルバムはえーっと 22時から販売開始で！ みんな買ってね！
The album sales start at 22:00! Everyone, please buy it!
holoXのみんな... 本当に4年目ありがとう！
To everyone in holoX... thank you so much for the 4th year!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
来年はもうholoXの 我々の年にしていくので 頑張ろうね！ / 5年目もよろしくお願いします！
Next year will be our year, holoX's year, so let's work hard! / Please support us in our 5th year too!
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to working with you!
じゃあみんな！ せーので行くよ！ せーの！ バイバイー！
Alright everyone! On three! Ready, go! Bye-bye!
解散！解散！ やったー！ バイバイー！
Dismissed! Dismissed! Yay! Bye-bye!